[
    {
      "question": "What is Thomas's sister name?",
      "answer": "Birdie",
      "points": 100,
      "num": "questionModal1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the intent of the author?",
      "answer": "Historical fiction",
      "points": 100,
      "num": "questionModal2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What year is it in the book?",
      "answer": "1863",
      "points": 100,
      "num": "questionModal3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why are the two sides fighting?",
      "answer": "To stop slavery",
      "points": 100,
      "num": "questionModal4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Henry reminds Thomas of who?",
      "answer": "Clem",
      "points": 200,
      "num": "questionModal5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Gettysburg located?",
      "answer": "Pennsylvania",
      "points": 200,
      "num": "questionModal6"
    },
    {
      "question": "How old is Thomas?",
      "answer": "11",
      "points": 200,
      "num": "questionModal7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did Thomas follow while traveling?",
      "answer": "The North Star",
      "points": 200,
      "num": "questionModal8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Thomas and Birdie save?",
      "answer": "Henry",
      "points": 300,
      "num": "questionModal9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did Thomas use as a weapon?",
      "answer": "A skunk",
      "points": 300,
      "num": "questionModal10"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Thomas help the soldiers?",
      "answer": "Brought them weapons",
      "points": 300,
      "num": "questionModal11"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the civil war?",
      "answer": "the Union Army",
      "points": 300,
      "num": "questionModal12"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who told who they should move?",
      "answer": "Henry told Thomas he should move",
      "points": 400,
      "num": "questionModal13"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did Henry tell Thomas to move to?",
      "answer": "Virginia",
      "points": 400,
      "num": "questionModal14"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did they find Thomas?",
      "answer": "The forest",
      "points": 400,
      "num": "questionModal15"
    },
    {
      "question": "What happened to Birdie during the battle?",
      "answer": "She was kidnapped",
      "points": 400,
      "num": "questionModal16"
    },
    {
      "question": "What two places does Thomas feel at home?",
      "answer": "The camp site Regement and Virginia",
      "points": 500,
      "num": "questionModal17"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Henry meet at the Regement camp site",
      "answer": "Henry, Captain Campbell, Homer, Lester",
      "points": 500,
      "num": "questionModal18"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the president during the Civil War?",
      "answer": "Abraham Lincoln",
      "points": 500,
      "num": "questionModal19"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the authors name?",
      "answer": "Lauren Tarshis",
      "points": 500,
      "num": "questionModal20"
    }
  ]